谢谢你
Thanks.
嗨  患者状况已经稳定了  他太太马上赶来
Hey. Our guy's stable. His wife's on the way.
不管怎么说  今天好歹一切都回归正轨
Well, it's nice that one thing went right today. Yeah.
嗨  韦伯医生
Hey, Dr. Webber.
我也不想在这里工作
I-I didn't want to work here, either.
你知道这种感觉吗  在格蕾-斯隆医院  我继承了很多馈赠
You know, at Grey-Sloan, I inherited a-a legacy.
我是贝莉的延续  你的延续
Bailey's legacy, your legacy.
你懂么  我的意思是  每当我做出选择时
You know, I mean, every choice I made,
你的声音萦绕在我耳畔  不要服输  要做的更好
I heard your voice in my head --"Don't settle. Do better."
在格蕾-斯隆医院  失败是我们最后的选择
At Grey-Sloan, failing was our last option.
但是在这里  失败是传统
But here, failure's the culture.
尽管如此  我们可以改变这一切
But we can change that.
我想说的是  死在格蕾-斯隆医院的手术室是一个选择
I mean, dying in an OR at Grey-Sloan is one plan,
但是也许  这里会有一个更适合你的选择
but maybe there is a better plan for you here.